{
  "level": 3,
  "unit": 4,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "An ________ is something that you worked hard to finish or learn.",
          "answer": "achievement"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you ________, you said you were sorry.",
          "answer": "apologized"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you give something your ________, you watch, listen, or concentrate on it.",
          "answer": "attention"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ________ is a group of people gathered to hear or see something.",
          "answer": "audience"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you have ________, you have trust or faith in something or someone.",
          "answer": "confidence"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you feel ________, you feel shy, uncomfortable, or ashamed.",
          "answer": "embarrassed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you ________ something, you became fully aware of it.",
          "answer": "realized"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ are natural abilities or skills.",
          "answer": "talents"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To________ is to give a warning or signal.",
          "answer": "alert"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ is a situation in which people or animals are trying to be more successful than others.",
          "answer": "competition"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ________ is the place that surrounds a living thing and affects its survival.",
          "answer": "environment"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ________ is very good.",
          "answer": "excellent"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To ________ is to like something better than another thing.",
          "answer": "prefer"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ is when something is kept safe.",
          "answer": "protection"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To be________ is to belong to the same family.",
          "answer": "related"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ is something that protects or covers something else.",
          "answer": "shelter"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "________ means willing to risk danger in order to have exciting or unusual experiences.",
          "answer": "adventurous"
        },
        { "prompt": "________ means very brave.", "answer": "courageous" },
        {
          "prompt": "________ means the same as “very.”",
          "answer": "extremely"
        },
        { "prompt": "________means strange or unusual.", "answer": "weird" },
        {
          "prompt": "________ is a form of poetry that does not have a regular pattern of rhyme and rhythm.",
          "answer": "free verse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ is a poem that tells a story.",
          "answer": "narrative poem"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ means that words or phrases in a poem are repeated for effect.",
          "answer": "repetition"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To ________ means to end with the same sound",
          "answer": "rhyme"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
